Guide to the Floyd J. McKay Research Files 1911-2002
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
Floyd J. McKay research files
1911-2002
Oregon Historical Society, Davies Family Research Library Research Library
Coll 449
McKay, Floyd J.
4.4 cubic ft. 4 record cartons, 1 flat box, and 34 audiocassette tapes.
Research files of author Floyd J. McKay pertaining to his 1998 biography of Charles A. Sprague, An Editor for Oregon: Charles A. Sprague and the Politics of Change.
Biographical Note
Floyd McKay (1935-), emeritus professor of journalism at Western Washington University, writes extensively on the history of journalism in the Pacific Northwest. Prior to his academic career, he worked as a reporter for the Oregon Statesman and as a news analyst for KGW television in Portland. While teaching at Western, he wrote guest columns and editorials for the Seattle Times.
The collection consists of research conducted by Floyd J. McKay for his biography of Charles A. Sprague entitled "An Editor for Oregon: Charles A. Sprague and the Politics of Change." Charles A. Sprague was governor of Oregon (1939-1943) and editor and manager of the Oregon Statesman. Materials include articles and clippings, correspondence, notes, and interviews with Sprague’s political and publishing associates and Sprague family members. Topics include civil rights and civil liberties, newspaper publishing, state and international politics, World War II, forestry and natural resources conservation.
The collection is arranged in the following series:
Series A: Research materials
Series B: Interviews
Order follows author's original file plan.
The collection is open to the public.
Lib. Acc. 28243
Audiocassette recordings from Accession 28243 are housed in the sound recording collection in the Oregon Historical Society Research Library.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
McKay, Floyd J.--Archives; Sprague, Charles A. (Charles Arthur), 1887-1969
Sprague family
Oregon Statesman (Salem, Or.)
Oregon -Politics and government - 1859-1950
Newspaper publishing - History; Newspaper editors - Oregon - Biography; Journalism - Oregon - History; Governors - Oregon - Biography; Civil rights - Oregon - History; World War, 1939-1945 - Oregon - History; Conservation of natural resources - Oregon - History
Journalism; Oregon; Politics and Politicians
Clippings; Interviews
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
- Research materials, 1911-2002; Series A; 4.2 cubic ft. (4 record cartons and 1 flat box)
  Series consists of newspaper and journal articles, correspondence, and other documents copied from various print and unpublished sources, as well as Floyd McKay's notes and some of his own published work.
  - Political issues
    - Civil rights, 1930s-1960s
      - Civil rights, liberties, 1963 (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Civil rights, 1940s (Box-folder 1/2)
      - Civil rights, liberties, 1930s (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Civil rights, 1948 (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Civil rights, 1945 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Housing, civil rights, 1949 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - Portland Public Accommodations, 1950 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - Civil rights, 1950s (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Civil rights, 1953 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Civil Rights Advisory, 1960 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Civil rights, 1960s (Box-folder 1/11)
    - House Unamerican Activities Committee (HUAC) - Portland - Civil Liberites, 1954
      - State employees loyalty oath, 1968 (Box-folder 1/12)
      - OSU Spitzer case, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Loyalty Oath, 1950 (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Teachers’ Oath- Editorials and news, 1951 (Box-folder 1/15)
      - Legislature, 1951 (Box-folder 1/16)
      - Mahoney, 1951 (Box-folder 1/17)
      - Lyle Nelson Eugene Register-Guard feature, 1997 (Box-folder 1/18)
      - HUAC editorials, 1954 (Box-folder 1/19)
      - Oregonian, 1954 (Box-folder 1/20)
      - Oregon Statesman, 1954 (Box-folder 1/21)
      - Oregon Journal, 1954 (Box-folder 1/22)
      - American Legion, 1950s (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Civil Liberties, 1930-1968
      - Tolon Committee, 1942 (Box-folder 1/24)
      - Pacific Northwest Quarterly article, 1997 (Box-folder 1/25)
      - Reed College, 1954 (Box-folder 1/26)
      - David Eyre - Reed College, 1997 (Box-folder 1/27)
      - Ford Foundation, 1954 (Box-folder 1/28)
      - McCarthy (Joseph McCarthy), 1950 (Box-folder 1/29)
      - McCarthy (Joseph McCarthy), 1951 (Box-folder 1/30)
      - McCarthy (Joseph McCarthy), 1952 (Box-folder 1/31)
      - McCarthy (Joseph McCarthy), 1953 (Box-folder 1/32)
      - McCarthy (Joseph McCarthy), 1954 (Box-folder 1/33)
      - Civil liberty, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 1/34)
      - Civil liberties, 1950s (Box-folder 1/35)
      - Civil liberties, 1960s (Box-folder 1/36)
      - John Birch Society, 1960s (Box-folder 1/37)
      - Gun control, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 1/38)
      - Capital punishment, 1949-1964 (Box-folder 1/39)
    - Indians - Fund for the Republic project
      - Indian Commission clippings, 1957; 1961 (Box-folder 1/40)
      - Indian Commission – archives, notes, undated (Box-folder 1/41)
      - Fund for Republic- Indians, 1957-1960; 1995 (Box-folder 1/42)
      - Legislature - Indians, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 1/43)
      - Klamath Indians, 1956-1957; 1964; 1967 (Box-folder 1/44)
      - Indians - miscellaneous clippings, 1933-1967 (Box-folder 1/45)
    - United Nations service, 1952
      - United Nations session, 1952 (Box-folder 1/46)
      - United States archives, 1953; undated (Box-folder 1/47)
      - Freedom of Information - United Nations, 1952 (Box-folder 1/48)
      - New York Times - United Nations, 1952 (Box-folder 1/49)
      - United Nations, pre-1952, 1944-1951 (Box-folder 1/50)
    - United Nations - International issues
      - United Nations - Foreign policy, 1953-1966 (Box-folder 1/51)
      - Israel, 1945-1961 (Box-folder 1/52)
      - McArthur, 1948-1951 (Box-folder 1/53)
      - Carnegie Endowment for Peace, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 1/54)
      - Atomic Bomb, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 1/55)
      - Vietnam, SE Asia (Southeast Asia), 1954-1967 (Box-folder 1/56)
      - Vietnam, 1968 (Box-folder 1/57)
    - Forestry, Wilderness, Conservation
      - Conservation, Natural Resources, 1939-1942 (Box-folder 1/58)
      - Outdoors, 1929-1964 (Box-folder 1/59)
      - Wilderness, 1957-1968 (Box-folder 1/60)
      - O&C Timber (Oregon & California Timber), 1946-1966 (Box-folder 1/61)
      - Getty- Bureau of Land Managment (BLM), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 1/62)
      - State Forest lands, 1945-1963 (Box-folder 1/63)
    - Government reorganization, Constitution
      - Government reorganization, 1960 (Box-folder 1/64)
      - Government reorganization, 1963 (Box-folder 1/65)
  - Politicians
    - Wayne Morse
      - Wayne Morse - Charles Sprague correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 1/66)
      - Morse (Wayne Morse), 1944 (Box-folder 1/67)
      - Morse (Wayne Morse), 1945-1950 (Box-folder 1/68)
      - Morse (Wayne Morse), 1950 (Box-folder 1/69)
      - Morse (Wayne Morse), 1951-1957 (Box-folder 1/70)
      - McKay - Morse (Douglas McKay and Wayne Morse), 1956 (Box-folder 1/71)
      - Morse (Wayne Morse), 1960 (Box-folder 1/72)
      - Morse (Wayne Morse), 1968 (Box-folder 1/73)
      - B. Whipple MA thesis on Wayne Morse, 1959 (Box-folder 1/74)
    - Richard Neuberger
      - Senate race, 1954 (Box-folder 1/75)
      - Neuberger, 1952-1959 (Box-folder 1/76)
  - State Government
    - Governor, 1939-1943
      - Inaugural, 1939 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Oregon Statesman, 1939 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Other newspaper clippings, 1939 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - McCarthy execution (Leroy Hershel McCarthy), 1939 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Personal, Political, 1939 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Legislature, 1939 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Governor, 1940
      - Campaign, 1940 (Box-folder 2/7)
      - McNary (Charles L. McNary), 1940 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1940 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Governor, 1941
      - Legislature, 1941 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1941 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Forestry plan (post-governor), 1938
      - Forestry, 1938-1942 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Forestry - post-governor, 1941-1998 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Governor - Miscellaneous
      - Prisons- Banks et al, 1939 (Box-folder 2/14)
        Note on folder: "OCF box 10" Contains photocopies from Special Collections, Knight Library, University of Oregon.
      - Governor - Miscellaneous, 1938-1942; 1997; undated (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Budget, taxes, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Gubernatorial campaign, 1942
      - Campaign documents, correspondence, 1942 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Campaign literature, 1942 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Voter registration statistics, 1942 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Snell speeches (Earl Snell gubernatorial campaign), 1942 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Tax - Multnomah County, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Oregonian - 1942 Primary (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Oregon Voter, 1942 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Oregon Journal - 1942 Primary (Box-folder 2/24)
      - News clippings – 1942 Primary (Box-folder 2/25)
    - Governor - personal
      - Staff, Administration, 1939; 1954 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Oregon Statesman during governorship, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 2/27)
    - Governor - World War II
      - December, 1941 December (Box-folder 2/28)
      - Oregon Militia, 1941-1945 (Box-folder 2/29)
      - Labor, 1941-1945 (Box-folder 2/30)
      - Miscellaneous, 1941-1945 (Box-folder 2/31)
      - American Legion, 1941-1945 (Box-folder 2/32)
      - World War II Industry, 1941-1945 (Box-folder 2/33)
      - Battleship Oregon, 1941-1959 (Box-folder 2/34)
      - V Days (Victory Days), 1945 (Box-folder 2/35)
    - Japanese Americans
      - Annotated copy of State Archives index to Sprague Papers (3/1) for war years, undated (Box-folder 2/36)
      - McKay notes to Charles Sprague correspondence - Japanese Americans, undated (Box-folder 2/37)
      - Japanese pre-war, 1941; undated (Box-folder 2/38)
      - Japan - Scrap Iron, 1939 (Box-folder 2/39)
      - Edits - JA (Editorials- Japanese Americans), 1941-1942 (Box-folder 2/40)
      - Clippings, 1942 (Box-folder 2/41)
      - Hood River, 1942 (Box-folder 2/42)
      - Japanese - Governor, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 2/43)
      - Army Public Relations program, undated (Box-folder 2/44)
      - Farm Labor- Japanese, 1942 (Box-folder 2/45)
      - Japanese- Personal stories, undated (Box-folder 2/46)
      - Japanese Relocation, 1940-1942; 1993 (Box-folder 2/47)
        Note on label: Box 4-76A-68 documents
      - Japanese deportation, 1943 (Box-folder 2/48)
      - Gresham area, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 2/49)
      - Legislature, anti-Japanese, 1945 (Box-folder 2/50)
      - Hood River, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 2/51)
      - Hood River News, American Legion, 1945 (Box-folder 2/52)
      - National press - Hood River, undated (Box-folder 2/53)
  - General and Political
    - General and political news clippings, 1943
      - Post-governor; general Oregon Statesman, 1943 (Box-folder 2/54)
      - Legislature, Snell, 1943 (Box-folder 2/55)
    - Senate Campaign, 1944
      - Campaign, 1944 (Box-folder 2/56)
      - Senate campaign, Oregon Statesman, 1944 (Box-folder 2/57)
      - Oregonian - Primary, 1944 (Box-folder 2/58)
      - Oregon Journal - Campaign, 1944 (Box-folder 2/59)
      - Other newspapers - Senate campaign, 1944 (Box-folder 2/60)
    - General, 1944-1949
      - Bush Pasture, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 2/61)
      - Miscellaneous Oregon Statesman, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 2/62)
      - 1947-1948 (Box-folder 2/63)
      - Election, 1948 (Box-folder 2/64)
      - Dewey-Stassen, 1948 (Box-folder 2/65)
      - Dewey-Stassen debate, Portland and Eugene newspapers, 1948 (Box-folder 2/66)
      - Oregon Statesman - Dewey-Stassen, 1948 (Box-folder 2/67)
    - General, 1950
      - Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box-folder 2/68)
      - Reapportionment, 1950 (Box-folder 2/69)
      - Constructed Week Study, 1950 (Box-folder 2/70)
    - General, 1951-1953
      - Presidential race, 1952 (Box-folder 2/71)
      - 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/72)
      - General, 1953 (Box-folder 2/73)
    - General, 1954-1958
      - Legislature, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 2/74)
      - Politics, 1956 (Box-folder 2/75)
      - Rackets, 1957 (Box-folder 2/76)
    - General, 1958-1962
      - Oregon Statesman -Governor’s race, 1958 (Box-folder 2/77)
      - General politics, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 2/78)
      - President, 1960 (Box-folder 2/79)
      - State politics, 1960 (Box-folder 2/80)
      - Legislature Mark O. Hatfield (MOH), 1961 (Box-folder 2/81)
      - Kennedy Administration, 191-1962 (Box-folder 2/82)
      - General - Oregon Statesman, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 2/83)
    - General, 1963-1966
      - Politics, legislature, 1963 (Box-folder 2/84)
      - General, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 2/85)
      - Presidential politics, 1964 (Box-folder 2/86)
      - Politics - General, Senate, 1966 (Box-folder 2/87)
      - 1966-1967 (Box-folder 2/88)
    - General, 1967-1968
      - President, 1968 (Box-folder 2/89)
      - General, 1968 (Box-folder 2/90)
  - Oregon Statesman
    - Oregon Statesman history
      - Oregon Statesman Pre-Charles Sprague, 1911-1928 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - 80th Anniversary Edition, 1931 March 28 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - 100 Years, 1951 March (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Oregon Statesman, 1930s (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Oregon Statesman, 1940s-1960s (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Oregon Statesman - 120th Anniversary, 1971 March 28 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Webb, W. – autobiography (Wendell Webb), undated (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Sheldon Sackett - Correspondence, notes, articles, 1930s-1971 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Oregon Statesman Post-Sprague
      - W. Webb (Wendell Webb), 1940-1982; 1996 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Sale to Gannett, 1974 (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Lawsuit- judgments, 1974; 1976 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - B. Spr. Stock (Robert Sprague), 1940; 1969; 1971 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - SJ Board (RWS) - (Statesman-Journal Board - Robert Sprague, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Wallace Sprague (WAS) - Robert Sprague (RWS) correspondence, 1958-1970 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Lawsuit - miscellaneous, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Statesman-Journal 150 Years, 2001 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Oregon Statesman coverage of assassination of President John F. Kennedy, 1963 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Oregon Statesman business records
      - Merger (Newport), 1954-1956; 1966-1967 (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Sale Offers, etc, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Economics, 1950s-1960s (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Failing Newspaper Act, 1969; 1971 (Box-folder 3/25)
      - Bonus Salaries Statesman, 1957-1969 (Box-folder 3/26)
      - News Budgets, 1942; 1957-1969 (Box-folder 3/27)
      - Circulation, 1954-1962 (Box-folder 3/28)
      - Circulation, 1928-1969 (Box-folder 3/29)
      - Circulation, 1958-1959; undated (Box-folder 3/30)
      - Property- 14th Street, taxes, 1947-1955 (Box-folder 3/31)
      - Property – Old Oregon Statesman Building, 1961 (Box-folder 3/32)
      - #12 Building Oregon Statesman - mortgage and architect, 1951-1969 (Box-folder 3/33)
      - McKay Business Comparisons, 1934-1947 (Box-folder 3/34)
      - Oregon Statesman - New Building, 1948; 1953 (Box-folder 3/35)
      - New Press, 19701 (Box-folder 3/36)
      - Television - Channel 3, undated (Box-folder 3/37)
      - Financial statements of The Oregon Statesman, 1928-1947 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Oregon Statesman advertising data
      - B. Sprague - Charles Nicholson correspondence, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 3/38)
      - Oregon Statesman Advertising, 1954-1965 (Box-folder 3/39)
      - Advertising, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 3/40)
      - Advertising campaign, 1958 (Box-folder 3/41)
      - Advertising, 1960s (Box-folder 3/42)
  - Other Publishing-Related Research
    - Industry data
      - Articles about newspapers, 1930-1992 (Box-folder 3/43)
      - 1920-1930s Era, 1924-1932 (Box-folder 3/44)
        Articles on newspaper costs and salaries.
      - Journalism Quarterly - Salaries, Economic Data, 1949; 1965; 1969 (Box-folder 3/45)
    - Oregon Publisher, Oregon Exchanges
      - Oregon Publisher, 1933; 1943 (Box-folder 4/27)
      - Oregon Exchanges, 1928-1931 (Box-folder 4/28)
      - Oregon Publisher, 1945-1955 (Box-folder 4/29)
    - Contemporary Oregon Editors
      - Oregon press and editors, 1924; 1950-1957; 1993 (Box-folder 4/30)
      - Eugene, Or. - William Tugman, Robert Frazier -articles and interviews, 1954-1961; 1993 (Box-folder 4/31)
      - E.B. MacNaughton, 1950; 1971 (Box-folder 4/32)
      - George Putnam, 1930; 1955; 1961; 1972 (Box-folder 4/33)
      - Robert Sawyer papers, University of Oregon guide, correspondence, William Lang paper; 1950s; 2010 (Box-folder 4/34)
      - C-J miscellaneous (Capital Journal), 1953-1982 (Box-folder 4/35)
      - Medford, Or. - Eric Allen, Robert W. Ruhl, 1950-1973 (Box-folder 4/36)
      - Oregon Journal - Marshall Dana, 1950 (Box-folder 4/37)
      - Pendleton, Or. - E.B. Aldrich, 1950 (Box-folder 4/38)
      - Corvallis, Or. - Claude Ingalls letter, 1944 (Box-folder 4/39)
    - Oregon Press, 1930-1960
      - Oregonian, article about history, 1976 (Box-folder 4/40)
      - Oregonian Sale, 1950 (Box-folder 4/41)
      - Cushman thesis, 1950 (Box-folder 4/42)
      - Editors - Other Studies, 1950s; 1963 (Box-folder 4/43)
      - Oregon journalism, 1940-1960 (Box-folder 4/44)
  - Charles A. Sprague - Personal and Other
    - Sprague biographies and obituaries
      - Biographies and Obituaries, 1969 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Oregon Statesman, post-Charles A. Sprague, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Charles A. Sprague 100th Anniversary, 1987 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Sprague family
      - Charles A. Sprague pre-Oregon life, 1887-1925 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Family information, 1920-1998 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Blanche Sprague, 1886-1976 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Martha Sprague (daughter), circa 1970; 1993 (Box-folder 4/7)
        Includes transcript of 1993 interview with Martha Sprague Hurley.
      - Wallace Sprague (son), 1992-1998 (Box-folder 4/8)
        Includes transcript of 1992 interview with Wallace Sprague.
      - Robert Sprague (nephew), 1929; 1976; 1994 (Box-folder 4/9)
        Includes transcript of 1994 interview with Robert Sprague, as well as Robert W. Sprague correspondence from 1929 and 1976.
      - Adams County Centennial Edition, 1883-1993 (Ritzville, Wash.), 1983 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Progressive Era
      - Prohibition, 1930 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Charles Sprague and the Progressives, 1912; 1924 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Wills, estate, finance
      - Moody’s - Stock, correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Stock, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Tax returns, 1943-1967 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Charles Sprague Estate and probate, 1935; 1965; 1969 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Church and YMCA, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Feature articles, speeches, honors and awards
      - Speeches on journalism, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Features, Specials, Awards for civil liberties, environment, 1962; 2002 (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Federal Boards, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - Charles Sprague on education, history, science, 1950-1966 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - General Research Materials
    - Archival and photo materials
      - State Archives - Inventory of Sprague papers and notes, undated (Box-folder 3/1)
      - OHS Boxes - Inventory of Oregon Historical Society collection and notes, undated (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Manuscripts, guide to, undated; Note on folder: see notebook #2 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Pictures for book, undated; Envelope, titled “Pix- Editor for Oregon” (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Photos, notes and correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Sprague papers (Ashard), correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 3/6)
        Correspondence with Judy Ashard, Wallace Sprague, and Chet Orloff regarding a failed bid for acquisition of the Sprague papers for the Oregon Historical Society.
    - Salem history, general
      - Salem - clippings, 1940-1968 (Box-folder 4/22)
      - Gerry Frank, interview notes; 1933; 1950-1955; 1991; 1996 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Venus statue, 1953; 1957 (Box-folder 4/24)
      - Salem history, 1930-1990 (Box-folder 4/25)
      - Salem history - notes by McKay, undated (Box-folder 4/26)
- Interviews and transcripts for book, 1969-1997; 1988-1997; Series B; 0.1 cubic ft (1 folder)
  - Interviews, 1988-1997 (Box-folder 4/21)
    Index to interviews conducted by Floyd McKay for his biography of Charles Sprague.
    See also folders 4/7 - 4/9
  - Oral history interview tapes, Subseries 1; Oral histories are also individually cataloged in the Oral History Collections, Oregon Historical Society Research Library.
    - SR 11420: Dorothy Crawford and George LaBorde, 1988 March 14; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11421: Travis Cross, 1991 August 27; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11422: Charles Davis, 1991 August 28; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11423: David Eccles, 1991 August 28; 2 audiocassettes
    - SR 11424: Cecil Edwards, 1991 August 28; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11425:Jeryme English, 1991 September 3; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11426: J. W. (Bud) Forrester, 1991 September 4; 2 audiocassettes
    - SR 11427: Robert E. Gangware, circa 1989; 2 audiocassettes
    - SR 11428: Roy Harland, circa 1989; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11429: Mark O. Hatfield, 1993 February 13; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11430: Paul W. Harvey, Jr., 1991 September 6; 2 audiocassettes
    - SR 11431: Al Lightner, 1994 January 18; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11432: Herb Lundy, 1992 July 9; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11433: William Mainwaring, 1996 September 18; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11464: Maurine Neuberger, 1992 July 8; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11465: Robert Notson, 1994 June 13; 2 audiocassettes
    - SR 11466: Conrad Prange, 1991 August 31; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11467: Blanche Sprague, 1969 December; 1 audiocassette
      Interviewer may have been J. Wesley Sullivan.
    - SR 11468: Martha Sprague Hurley, 1993 February 25; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11484: Robert Sprague, 1994 January 16; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11485: Wallace Sprauge, 1992 August 4; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11486: J. Wesley Sullivan, 1994 June 10; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11487: Marguerite Wright, 1992 July 30; 1 audiocassette
    - SR 11488: Thomas J. Wright, Jr., 1989 August 29; 3 audiocassettes
    - SR 11489: Statesman Oldtimers, 1988 August 14; 2 audiocassettes
      Interviews of several longtime newsroom employees, recorded by J. Wesley Sullivan.
    - SR 11490: Cecil Edwards/Paul Harvey, 1988 August 16; 1 audiocassette